<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sudoku e il calice di Android</string>
    <string name="difficulty">Difficulty</string>
    <string name="sudoku">Sudoku</string>
    <string name="group">Il calice di Android</string>
    <string name="new_game">New game</string>
    <string name="load_game">Load game</string>
    <string name="rules">Rules</string>
    <string name="wrong">Wrong</string>
    <string name="won">You won!</string>
    <string name="game_complete">Game Complete!</string>
    <string name="total_time">"Total Time: "</string>
    <string name="mistakes">"Mistakes: "</string>
    <string name="rules01">The rule: never the same number.</string>
    <string name="rules02">There is only one rule for playing Sudoku: you have to fill the board in such a way that each row, each column and each square contain the numbers from 1 to 9. The condition is that no row, no column or square has the same twice number.</string>
    <string name="rules03">The advice: use reasoning. Each number entered correctly is additional information to find the others.</string>
    <string name="rules04">Example: we use the square shown above as an example to suggest some logical techniques to start playing. Look at the 7s in the vertical series to the left of the three boxes. There is a 7 in the upper box, a 7 in the lower box, but there is no 7 in the central one. The 7 in the top box applies to the entire first column, the 7 in the bottom box also applies to the entire second column. So the 7 that we have to put in the middle box will not go to the first and second column, but to the third. Within the central box, the third column already has two boxes filled in and only one free. That box (marked in the example with the letter A) is the only one that can contain the 7. Now we see the 7 in the series of boxes at the top of the grid. The 7 is in the left pane and there is also in the right one, missing in the central pane. The 7 of the box on the right is valid for the whole first row, the 7 of the box on the left is valid for the whole second row of boxes. Using the previous logical technique we know that in this case the 7 must be entered in box B or box C. But in the first column of the second box there is a 7, while there is no in the second. Consequently, the 7 should be placed where the letter C is. Going forward and examining the central squares and always the number 7 we see that it is missing in the square to the right of the middle sequence. According to the same reasoning already made previously, it is clear that the 7 goes where we put the letter D.</string>
    <string name="rules05">The tools: pencil, an eraser to erase any errors, info for suggestions and go back to delete the last number entered. Start with the numbers that are most present and remember that for each game the solution is one and only one.</string>
    <string name="game_over">Game Over</string>
    <string name="easy">Easy</string>
    <string name="normal">Normal</string>
    <string name="hard">Hard</string>
    <string name="expert">Expert</string>
    <string name="note">Note</string>
    <string name="clue">Clue</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="no_game">There\'s no game to load</string>
    <string name="game_saved">Game Saved</string>
    <string name="select">Select the cell first</string>
    <string name="scores">SCORES</string>
</resources>